[
	{
		"questionText":"1+1",
		"answerOne":"1",
		"answerTwo":"2",
		"answerThree":"3",
		"answerFour":"4",
		"correctAns":1,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"2+2",
		"answerOne":"8",
		"answerTwo":"6",
		"answerThree":"4",
		"answerFour":"2",
		"correctAns":2,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"9X9",
		"answerOne":"18",
		"answerTwo":"33",
		"answerThree":"81",
		"answerFour":"88",
		"correctAns":2,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"7-3",
		"answerOne":"4",
		"answerTwo":"1",
		"answerThree":"3",
		"answerFour":"7",
		"correctAns":0,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"0X0",
		"answerOne":"1",
		"answerTwo":"2",
		"answerThree":"7",
		"answerFour":"0",
		"correctAns":3,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"34-32",
		"answerOne":"3",
		"answerTwo":"2",
		"answerThree":"30",
		"answerFour":"5",
		"correctAns":1,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"12-2",
		"answerOne":"10",
		"answerTwo":"4",
		"answerThree":"14",
		"answerFour":"0",
		"correctAns":0,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"66+1",
		"answerOne":"66",
		"answerTwo":"68",
		"answerThree":"69",
		"answerFour":"67",
		"correctAns":3,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"99+2",
		"answerOne":"100",
		"answerTwo":"101",
		"answerThree":"102",
		"answerFour":"103",
		"correctAns":1,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"8x3",
		"answerOne":"8",
		"answerTwo":"11",
		"answerThree":"16",
		"answerFour":"24",
		"correctAns":3,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"4+5",
		"answerOne":"10",
		"answerTwo":"20",
		"answerThree":"9",
		"answerFour":"11",
		"correctAns":2,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"1+1",
		"answerOne":"1",
		"answerTwo":"2",
		"answerThree":"3",
		"answerFour":"4",
		"correctAns":1,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"2+2",
		"answerOne":"8",
		"answerTwo":"6",
		"answerThree":"4",
		"answerFour":"2",
		"correctAns":2,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"9X9",
		"answerOne":"18",
		"answerTwo":"33",
		"answerThree":"81",
		"answerFour":"88",
		"correctAns":2,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"7-3",
		"answerOne":"4",
		"answerTwo":"1",
		"answerThree":"3",
		"answerFour":"7",
		"correctAns":0,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"0X0",
		"answerOne":"1",
		"answerTwo":"2",
		"answerThree":"7",
		"answerFour":"0",
		"correctAns":3,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"34-32",
		"answerOne":"3",
		"answerTwo":"2",
		"answerThree":"30",
		"answerFour":"5",
		"correctAns":1,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"12-2",
		"answerOne":"10",
		"answerTwo":"4",
		"answerThree":"14",
		"answerFour":"0",
		"correctAns":0,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"66+1",
		"answerOne":"66",
		"answerTwo":"68",
		"answerThree":"69",
		"answerFour":"67",
		"correctAns":3,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"99+2",
		"answerOne":"100",
		"answerTwo":"101",
		"answerThree":"102",
		"answerFour":"103",
		"correctAns":1,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"8x3",
		"answerOne":"8",
		"answerTwo":"11",
		"answerThree":"16",
		"answerFour":"24",
		"correctAns":3,
		"rank":1
	},
	{
		"questionText":"4+5",
		"answerOne":"10",
		"answerTwo":"20",
		"answerThree":"9",
		"answerFour":"11",
		"correctAns":2,
		"rank":1
	}
]








